In this assignment we will create a new project,
在这项任务中， 我们将创建一个 新的
import our assets, save our main scene
项目导入 我们的资产 保存 主要
and set up the basic foundations for our game.
现场并设置 基础
Let's begin by creating a brand new project.
对于我们的游戏，让我们开始 创建一个
We can do this by selecting File - New Project.
全新的项目， 我们可以做到这一点
This opens the Project Wizard.
选择文件新项目 打开
That's it for setting up this project.
现在就称之为太空射击游戏
Now that we've setup the project, in the next
我已经改变了我的布局，我 可以回
assignment we will setup the main player game object.
这个只需从中选择它
That's it for setting up this project.
现在就称之为太空射击游戏
Now that we've setup the project, in the next
我已经改变了我的布局，我 可以回
assignment we will setup the main player game object.
这个只需从中选择它
布局下拉菜单就是这样的